export const nature =  [
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20considered%20the%20rarist%20form%20of%20color%20blindness%3F",
"correct_answer": "Blue",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Red",
"Green",
"Purple"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20liquids%20is%20least%20viscous%3F%20Assume%20temperature%20is%2025%C2%B0C.",
"correct_answer": "Acetone",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Water",
"Mercury",
"Benzene"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "The%20%27Islets%20of%20Langerhans%27%20is%20found%20in%20which%20human%20organ%3F",
"correct_answer": "Pancreas",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Kidney",
"Liver",
"Brain"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "How%20many%20legs%20is%20it%20biologically%20impossible%20for%20a%20centipede%20to%20have%3F",
"correct_answer": "100",
"incorrect_answers": [
"26",
"50",
"74"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20common%20name%20is%20given%20to%20the%20medial%20condition%2C%20tibial%20stress%20syndrome%20%28MTSS%29%3F",
"correct_answer": "Shin%20Splints",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Tennis%20Elbow",
"Carpal%20Tunnel",
"Housemaid%27s%20Knee"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20molecular%20formula%20of%20Glucose%3F",
"correct_answer": "C6H12O6",
"incorrect_answers": [
"C2H4O2",
"K%2B",
"CH4"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "An%20organic%20compound%20is%20considered%20an%20alcohol%20if%20it%20has%20what%20functional%20group%3F",
"correct_answer": "Hydroxyl",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Carbonyl",
"Alkyl",
"Aldehyde"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "All%20of%20the%20following%20human%20genetic%20haplogroup%20names%20are%20shared%20between%20Y-chromosome%20and%20mitochondrial%20DNA%20haplogroups%20EXCEPT%3A",
"correct_answer": "Haplogroup%20U",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Haplogroup%20L",
"Haplogroup%20T",
"Haplogroup%20J"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20horizon%20in%20a%20soil%20profile%20consists%20of%20bedrock%3F",
"correct_answer": "R",
"incorrect_answers": [
"O",
"B",
"D"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20scientific%20name%20of%20the%20knee%20cap%3F",
"correct_answer": "Patella",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Femur",
"Foramen%20Magnum",
"Scapula"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "If%20you%20planted%20the%20seeds%20of%20Quercus%20robur%20what%20would%20grow%3F",
"correct_answer": "Trees",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Flowers",
"Vegtables",
"Grains"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20chemical%20compounds%20is%20NOT%20found%20in%20gastric%20acid%3F",
"correct_answer": "Sulfuric%20acid",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Hydrochloric%20acid",
"Potassium%20chloride",
"Sodium%20chloride"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20scientific%20name%20of%20the%20red%20fox%3F",
"correct_answer": "Vulpes%20Vulpes",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Vulpes%20Redus",
"Red%20Fox",
"Vulpes%20Vulpie"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20is%20not%20a%20type%20of%20neuron%3F",
"correct_answer": "Perceptual%20Neuron",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Sensory%20Neuron",
"Motor%20Neuron",
"Interneuron"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Folic%20acid%20is%20the%20synthetic%20form%20of%20which%20vitamin%3F",
"correct_answer": "Vitamin%20B",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Vitamin%20A",
"Vitamin%20C",
"Vitamin%20D"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "%22The%20Big%20Bang%20Theory%22%20was%20first%20theorized%20by%20a%20priest%20of%20what%20religious%20ideology%3F",
"correct_answer": "Catholic",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Christian",
"Jewish",
"Islamic"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20moon%20is%20the%20only%20satellite%20in%20our%20solar%20system%20to%20possess%20a%20dense%20atmosphere%3F",
"correct_answer": "Titan",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Europa",
"Miranda",
"Callisto"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20molecular%20formula%20of%20Ozone%3F",
"correct_answer": "O3",
"incorrect_answers": [
"C6H2O6",
"N2O",
"SO4"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "The%20core%20of%20the%20Sun%20can%20reach%20which%20temperature%3F",
"correct_answer": "27%C2%B0%20Million%20F%20%2815%C2%B0%20Million%20C%29",
"incorrect_answers": [
"938%2C000%C2%B0%20F%20%28521093.3%C2%B0%20C%29",
"8%C2%B0%20Billion%20F%20%28%C2%B04.4%20Billion%20C%29",
"Absolute%20Zero%20%28Both%20F%20and%20C%29"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20plastic%20is%20commonly%20used%20for%20window%20frames%2C%20gutters%20and%20drain%20pipes%3F",
"correct_answer": "Polyvinylchloride%20%28PVC%29%20",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Polyethylene%20%28PE%29",
"Polypropylene%20%28PP%29",
"Polystyrene%20%28PS%29"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20element%20on%20the%20periodic%20table%20has%2092%20electrons%3F",
"correct_answer": "Uranium",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Sulfur",
"Hydrogen",
"Iron"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20genetic%20disease%20is%20caused%20by%20having%20an%20extra%20Y%20chromosome%20%28XYY%29%3F",
"correct_answer": "Jacob%27s%20Syndrome",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Klinefelter%27s%20Syndrome",
"Turner%27s%20Syndrome",
"Down%20Syndrome"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Botanically%20speaking%2C%20which%20of%20these%20fruits%20is%20NOT%20a%20berry%3F",
"correct_answer": "Strawberry",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Blueberry",
"Banana",
"Concord%20Grape"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20does%20the%20term%20%22isolation%22%20refer%20to%20in%20microbiology%3F",
"correct_answer": "The%20separation%20of%20a%20strain%20from%20a%20natural%2C%20mixed%20population%20of%20living%20microbes",
"incorrect_answers": [
"A%20lack%20of%20nutrition%20in%20microenviroments",
"The%20nitrogen%20level%20in%20soil",
"Testing%20effects%20of%20certain%20microorganisms%20in%20an%20isolated%20enviroments%2C%20such%20as%20caves"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "How%20much%20radiation%20does%20a%20banana%20emit%3F",
"correct_answer": "0.1%20Microsievert",
"incorrect_answers": [
"0.3%20Microsievert",
"0.5%20Microsievert",
"0.7%20Microsievert"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20unit%20of%20electrical%20inductance%3F",
"correct_answer": "Henry",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Weber",
"Coulomb",
"Mho"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Muscle%20fiber%20is%20constructed%20of%20bundles%20small%20long%20organelles%20called%20what%3F",
"correct_answer": "Myofibrils",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Epimysium",
"Myofiaments",
"Myocardium"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20is%20NOT%20a%20word%20used%20to%20describe%20an%20earthquake%3F",
"correct_answer": "Drop-slide",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Foreshock",
"Strike-slip",
"Temblor"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Where%20is%20the%20Gluteus%20Maximus%20muscle%20located%3F",
"correct_answer": "Butt",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Arm",
"Head",
"Torso"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "How%20long%20is%20a%20light-year%3F",
"correct_answer": "9.461%20Trillion%20Kilometres",
"incorrect_answers": [
"1%20AU",
"105.40%20Earth-years",
"501.2%20Million%20Miles"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20scientific%20name%20for%20the%20extinct%20hominin%20known%20as%20%22Lucy%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Australopithecus%20Afarensis",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Australopithecus%20Africanus",
"Australopithecus%20Architeuthis",
"Australopithecus%20Antaris"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20is%20the%20term%20for%20%22surgical%20complications%20resulting%20from%20surgical%20sponges%20left%20inside%20the%20patient%27s%20body%3F",
"correct_answer": "Gossypiboma",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Gongoozler",
"Jentacular",
"Meupareunia"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Coulrophobia%20is%20the%20irrational%20fear%20of%20what%3F",
"correct_answer": "Clowns",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Cemeteries",
"Needles",
"Tunnels"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "The%20Western%20Lowland%20Gorilla%20is%20scientifically%20know%20as%3F",
"correct_answer": "Gorilla%20Gorilla%20Gorilla",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Gorilla%20Gorilla%20Diehli",
"Gorilla%20Beringei%20Graueri",
"Gorilla%20Beringei%20Beringei"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20%22Stenoma%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "A%20genus%20of%20moths",
"incorrect_answers": [
"A%20combat%20stimulant%20from%20WW2",
"A%20type%20of%20seasoning",
"A%20port%20city%20in%20the%20carribean"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20scientific%20unit%20is%20named%20after%20an%20Italian%20nobleman%3F",
"correct_answer": "Volt",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Pascal",
"Ohm",
"Hertz"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Autosomal-dominant%20Compelling%20Helio-Ophthalmic%20Outburst%20syndrome%20is%20the%20need%20to%20do%20what%20when%20seeing%20the%20Sun%3F",
"correct_answer": "Sneeze",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Cough",
"Yawn",
"Hiccup"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20physics%20principle%20relates%20the%20net%20electric%20flux%20out%20of%20a%20closed%20surface%20to%20the%20charge%20enclosed%20by%20that%20surface%3F",
"correct_answer": "Gauss%27s%20Law",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Faraday%27s%20Law",
"Ampere%27s%20Law",
"Biot-Savart%20Law"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20animals%20belongs%20in%20class%20Chondrichthyes%3F",
"correct_answer": "Great%20white%20shark",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Octopus",
"Killer%20whale",
"Catfish"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "The%20word%20%22science%22%20stems%20from%20the%20word%20%22scire%22%20meaning%20what%3F",
"correct_answer": "To%20know",
"incorrect_answers": [
"To%20measure",
"To%20live",
"To%20count"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20elements%20is%20typically%20used%20in%20the%20doping%20of%20the%20semiconductor%20silicon%3F",
"correct_answer": "Boron",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Oxygen",
"Carbon",
"Iron"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20major%20extinction%20event%20was%20caused%20by%20an%20asteroid%20collision%20and%20eliminated%20the%20majority%20of%20non-avian%20dinosaurs%3F",
"correct_answer": "Cretaceous-Paleogene",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Triassic%E2%80%93Jurassic",
"Permian%E2%80%93Triassic",
"Ordovician%E2%80%93Silurian"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20for%20the%20auditory%20illusion%20of%20a%20note%20that%20seems%20to%20be%20rising%20infinitely%3F",
"correct_answer": "Shepard%20Tone",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Glissandro%20Illusion",
"Fransen%20Effect",
"McGurck%20Effect"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20most%20potent%20toxin%20known%3F",
"correct_answer": "Botulinum%20toxin",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Ricin",
"Cyanide",
"Asbestos"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20is%20a%20major%20muscle%20of%20the%20back%3F",
"correct_answer": "Trapezius",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Trapezium",
"Trapezoid",
"Triquetrum"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20is%20considered%20classical%20conditioning%3F",
"correct_answer": "Pavlov%27s%20dog%20experiments",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Skinner%20box%20experiment",
"Schr%C3%B6dinger%27s%20cat%20experiment",
"Harlow%E2%80%99s%20monkey%20experiments"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20causes%20the%20sound%20of%20a%20heartbeat%3F",
"correct_answer": "Closure%20of%20the%20heart%20valves",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Cntraction%20of%20the%20heart%20chambers",
"Blood%20exiting%20the%20heart",
"Relaxation%20of%20the%20heart%20chambers"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "In%20quantum%20physics%2C%20which%20of%20these%20theorised%20sub-atomic%20particles%20has%20yet%20to%20be%20observed%3F",
"correct_answer": "Graviton",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Z%20boson",
"Tau%20neutrino",
"Gluon"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "In%20the%20Scoville%20scale%2C%20what%20is%20the%20hottest%20chemical%3F",
"correct_answer": "Resiniferatoxin",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Capsaicin",
"Dihydrocapsaicin",
"Tinyatoxin"
]
},
{
"category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "In%20physics%2C%20conservation%20of%20energy%20and%20conservation%20of%20momentum%20are%20both%20consequences%20of%20which%20of%20the%20following%3F",
"correct_answer": "Noether%27s%20Theorem",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Bell%27s%20Theorem",
"Wick%27s%20Theorem",
"Carnot%27s%20Theorem"
]
}
]